

GEORGE SAGIANNIS

▶ 6931151049 Personal Website/Portfolio: https://portfolio-2pq2.onrender.com/

■ gsagiannis@gmail.com LinkedIn <u>www.linkedin.com/in/george-sagiannis/</u>

• Thrakis 8 Athens - Tavros GitHub Projects: https://github.com/george-sagiannis

SUMMARY

Experienced Front End Developer with 10 years of experience building and maintaining responsive websites and applications using especially HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript (vanilla or React.js). Holds a Bachelor's Degree in Applied Informatics in Management & Finance from the Higher Technological Educational Institute of Messolonghi.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

UpcoMinds Ltd. Nov 2022 - Present

- Customer Care Web Application with HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, and Ajax for HEDNO
- Customer Care Back Office Application with HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, and Ajax for HEDNO

Front End Developer

Green Properties

Jun 2021 - Nov 2022

- Design, Development and Maintenance Websites (most known (greenpropertiesdc.com, ultra-glass.com, luxandeasy.com, topsmartinv.com, novaconstructionssa.com, tolmidis.gr, us.neon-energy.com etc.)
- Administrator of Plesk (Domains (90 +), Mail Configurations, PHP updates, Server Storage Backups especially for the Websites)
- Basic support in Front Office Website Admin Panel (Terra ERP for https://www.362grocery.com/)

Front End Developer

Express Publishing

Jun 2015 - Jun 2021

- Development of interactive applications (Digital Books) with HTML5, CSS3, Javascript
- Moodle Development
- Responsive Web Design Development and Maintenance (https://epiebooks.com/)

Web Developer

NV -Office

Jan 2013 – Apr 2015

• Design, Development, Maintenance and Optimization of Websites (SEO, PHP, MySQL, HTML5/CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, Ajax)

EDUCATION

SKILLS

Technical skills:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Javascript
- JQuery
- Ajax
- Bootstrap
- SASS
- Plesk

- React.js
- Redux
- Jest
- Wordpress
- CMS
- GIT
- CRM
- ERP

Soft skills:

- Communication skills
- Adaptability
- Problem-solving
- Critical Thinking

- Teamwork
- Time management
- Creativity
- Collaboration

CERTIFICATIONS & LICENSES

- IT Specialist Web Developer (MySQL, PHP, HTML, Dreamweaver CS4) for KeyCERT (06/07/10)
- (A1) Received and transmitted orders for transferable securities at the Capital Market Commission (02/12/13), though the certification has expired in (02/12/16)
- React Nanodegree Certificate from Udacity (09/10/2023)

SEMINARS

- Whatever has relationship with Front End Development and Web Development (over 10 courses on Udemy) Present
- Web Development (MySQL, PHP, HTML, Dreamweaver CS4) at IEK OMIROS (Duration: 72 hours, March May 2010)
- Machine Accounting (Atlantis ERP) at the Free Studies Center (Duration: 60 hours, August 12, 2010 February 4, 2011)

LANGUAGES

- Greek Mother Tongue
- English FCE Cambridge, 2000
- German Basic knowledge

OTHER

	OTHER
•	Cinema, Music, Theatre, Information Technology, Finance, Sports, Travelling, Reading and Studying Books Military Obligations: (Completed - During my studies at the Higher Technological Educational Institute of Messolonghi I completed my military obligations for 1 year)